(Leonard:)Friends overlook
each other's minor lapses.
(Leonard:)For the record, Howard, I'm
sorry that I broke our pact.
Thank you.
(Howard:)And I'm sorry
about your phone
(Howard:)and Thanksgiving.
(Howard:)And while we're at it,
(Howard:)you don't have to wash our
clothes on the Fourth of July.
As long as we're apologizing,
Sheldon, I'm, I'm sorry
I used your toothbrush.
(Howard:)And I'm sorry...
but that behavior
is beyond the pale
(Sheldon:)and cannot be tolerated.
(Sheldon:)We are no longer friends.
(Raj:)I got you a talking Thomas the
Tank Engine for Thanksgiving.
(Sheldon:)With real puffing smoke?
(Howard:)Yes.
All right.
(Sheldon:)But I'm watching you.
Hey, you've got Snoopy out.
Can I have a snow cone?
(Sheldon:)Well, sure.
This is pretty good.
What flavor is this?
(Raj:)Guess.
(Leonard:)Papaya?
No.
(Leonard:)Guava?
You're so close.
(Leonard:)I give up.
(Sheldon:)Mango caterpillar.
(Leonard:)What are
you doing?!
(Sheldon:)You said you
liked it.